Today, I'm going to share with you how 3D technology helps our traditional trade industry.
First of all, I'm going to share my thoughts on these four aspects.
The first one is an introduction to the Guangdong Provincial Law.
The second one is the promotion and effect of 3D clothing on trade.
The third one is the presentation of 3D products to our colleagues and the outlook on the future.
Guangdong Provincial Law was established in 1949.
As I just mentioned, we are a state-owned enterprise that is the first to engage in foreign trade in the clothing industry in Huanan.
We have more than 500 fabric factories and more than 200 cotton factories.
We are the vice-chairman of the China Provincial Exports and Exports Association.
Tongzhuang and Niuzai are the leading companies in China.
Our company produces the first China-exported jeans.
We have branches in many places in the United States, Singapore, Shanghai, and Ireland.
Our company has been using 3D for a relatively long time.
We started using 3D in 2008,
because the company's leaders saw the future use of 3D.
At the beginning, we used Optex.
At that time, it was TD3.
Later, in 2018, we started to use Claw.
It is a comprehensive improvement.
We have also started to use 3D software that is more well-known in the industry.
Our team has also been constantly expanding,
and we have obtained some related certifications from many major customers.
This one is a demonstration of 3D.
From 2017 to 2023,
we have seen a change in 3D samples and physical samples.
Our physical samples have been constantly decreasing.
However, our 3D samples have been constantly increasing.
All kinds of customers have been using 3D samples.
The use of 3D samples since 2008 has been a huge growth.
In 2019, because of the pandemic,
the use of 3D samples has been growing rapidly.
Because of the pandemic,
although our clothing industry has not opened,
our clothing industry has not been able to stop.
Therefore, we have adopted a virtual skin.
We can ensure that our samples cannot be sent out,
but our samples' skin will not stop.
Our production will not be interrupted.
Here, we have made a comparison of 3D samples and traditional samples.
3D online research and development
has been compressed to 3 to 7 days.
In the traditional industry,
it takes 15 to 60 days from the beginning to the end.
In the middle, the time is significantly reduced.
The cost is also compressed and reduced.
Therefore, our 3D usage is getting higher and higher.
3D has played a role in the promotion of our clothing industry.
Because the current industry is a consumer market,
there is a decline in the purchasing power of consumers.
And there are many new customers who experience consumption.
Our brand is facing a high storage pressure,
and it is facing environmental and social responsibility challenges.
So the brand was originally a large order,
but it has been reduced to a small order.
And there is a prejudice against the market,
and it is becoming more and more conservative.
Therefore, the competition of our foreign trade companies is getting more and more internalized.
As the global economy becomes more and more integrated,
the Chinese foreign trade industry faces many challenges.
It needs continuous innovation and breakthrough.
So how do we improve the competitiveness of our companies
to deal with the changes in the market and the pressure of the entire competition?
Well, 3D is a new track.
It can shorten our development cycle.
The cost can also be reduced.
So we have found a new breakthrough.
It allows our designers to present a sample from the design to the final product.
It can be faster and become a new track for us to stand out.
3D can obviously reduce the cost of our samples.
It can reduce the cost of our samples,
reduce the cost of physical logistics,
and save a total cost of a development stage.
And 3D has also optimized our entire inventory.
Because the sample pile needs space.
So now we can store it in 3D.
It also saves the cost of our sample storage.
And it improves efficiency and cost control.
It can make us more competitive.
So it strengthens the ability of foreign trade companies in the international market.
Now everyone is talking about environmental protection.
If we use 3D,
we can reduce the waste of materials.
It is more in line with the environmental protection concept.
And in the production of samples,
it is inevitable that there will be some waste of cotton.
Most of the time, samples cannot pass in one go.
The samples that have not passed will also cause waste.
But 3D can make us more environmentally friendly.
This also reflects the social responsibility of our company.
3D can break through a hell.
Because many times,
just like what we said earlier,
3D samples cannot be sent out.
But with 3D,
I can send an email.
I can show it to customers in a better 360 degree way.
And unlike before,
when we go to sell to customers,
we sell large, small, large and small samples.
But for many samples,
I can't take them with me.
But with 3D,
I can use one model
to show all of our different fabrics
and different colors.
I can show them to customers in a better way.
And through 3D,
we can attract new customers.
Especially for some young consumers
who have high requirements for high-tech and new experiences.
Combined with social media and network marketing,
3D products show that
we can increase the interaction between users
and increase the exposure of the brand on the Internet.
The advantage of this product is that the cost is low.
The cost is low because I save the cost of logistics
and the cost of some face masks,
as well as the cost of some artificial samples,
including the cost of some machines and places of production.
So this short period of time,
because we talked about it earlier,
I basically have to wait for the face masks
for a whole time.
But now,
from the production of the fabric to the production of a sample,
it's fast and simple.
I only need two hours.
It's slow,
and it can be completed in one or two days.
And it's also easy to modify.
From a normal traditional clothes,
if we basically take out the clothes,
you can modify the simple parts,
but the big parts are basically wasted.
But 3D samples can be adjusted and modified at any time.
And it can also be used as a sample.
All the communication with the customer is also more convenient.
It can show more forms.
I will show you the diversity of our 3D samples later.
We can use different forms to better show our products.
We can interact better with customers.
We can interact with consumers.
And all of our 3D can be better digitized.
We can effectively collect some of these 3D data
to make it more.
It can also help us in some development.
The most important thing is the environment.
This is a problem that we are all concerned about all over the world.
Next, we will show some of our team's 3D products.
Usually, we basically have the same needs with our customers.
Because of different knowledge,
because in different stores,
they have to show our products in different ways.
We have a 3D store to show our clothes.
It has a lot of hanging,
flat shoes,
folding effects,
and we have these woolen clothes here.
It has some fabric effects.
These are our bullfrogs.
On the side, this is a physical sample.
A 3D sample.
It can be very good.
I don't need the hardener to open the mold.
But I can show my 3D models.
to show the effect of my real body
to the customer.
If the customer needs to change the pattern
or change the design,
it's all very fast.
The style of the cow is the same.
All kinds of washing effects
can be predicted in advance by the customer.
Is this washing effect what he wants?
This is also a comparison between the real body and 3D.
Before we probably have
a 부분 in front,
we can basically see the effect of this sample before then.
This is the sweater
We can see the texture
from sc dobrar
to we created sweater.
to make some recommendations to the customers.
Now the most important thing for us is that we have a lot of jumpers.
For example, I have already made a traditional chicken horse.
When I want to make a jumpers,
I can use 3D.
The jumpers are basically riding horses.
If I ride a horse, I need to make a sample of many pieces.
When I use a jumpers,
after using 3D,
I can save a lot of cost of making a sample.
Also, we will use some products with different scenarios,
different configurations and homes.
Of course, our team will often do some show-offs.
For example, we often participate in fairs.
In the past, we needed to make a lot of products.
But now we can quickly use the ideas and ideas of the designers
to show our overall design effect in a show-off way.
In addition, we have also made some VR booths.
This is what we think is relatively useful now.
Traditionally, we often need a piece of clothing.
I need to use my real person to try on its comfort.
Because we are very special, it is a coat.
If you are a child,
you often go to class and go to school.
We need to make an appointment with a model.
It is more difficult.
Now we are making a model.
I will use a 3D model to test it.
When it is running or moving,
how is its growth and extension?
Now we also have a 3D model.
We can quickly use AI to change the makeup
and change the skin and the effect.
For example, this is a client group in Europe and the United States.
I can change to Europe and the United States.
If I am in the United States,
I can change to a different face in front of a different client group.
This can quickly save the cost of taking pictures.
This can be quickly applied to our e-commerce.
It can speed up our up-to-date speed.
These are some of the styles we started with.
We can quickly use AI and 3D to pre-sale without matching.
What is the future outlook?
In the future, I believe the continuous optimization of the software
should be what our company expects.
I think Cloud has always been determined to update the software
and actively cooperate with our company.
So we are very grateful to Cloud for its cooperation with us.
Another one is the optimization of the technology
such as AI and big data.
We are very happy with the technology.
In the future, we will use the technology to
optimize our 3D design to make it more intelligent and automated.
In the future, we will use the technology to show the future
with VR and AR.
We can be better than customers
to promote our virtual samples,
to make it more popular in the three-art world.
Some of the pre-sale predictions are 3D design,
and the general applications in the clothing industry.
I believe that 3D design will become a new standard tool for the clothing industry,
and it will greatly promote the digital transformation of the clothing industry.
Because now, many times, like our company,
before a sample is developed, we will first test the fabric.
So now, modeling is not a difficulty for us.
Many times, we need to match the reality with the real fabric,
and this is what we are currently trying to do.
So the future may be to increase the 3D fabric,
which will greatly enhance the 3D application.
3D technology will also become a part of the 3D outerwear standard process,
because as everyone knows,
our outerwear is much better
than the 3D fabric. because as everyone knows, our outerwear is much better than the 3D fabric.
We also need more flexible, more efficient cross-border e-commerce business.
So this will be more efficient to use this 3D technology.
A comprehensive upgrade of the manufacturing industry.
So now we are also an intelligent production.
In the future, 3D is a paper board.
We basically use a lot of things in 3D now.
For example, my style, my craftsmanship has been confirmed.
When my board is also confirmed,
we don't need to make real samples anymore.
We can directly make some small changes after 3D is done.
After looking at the style,
we can directly use it to make it.
The impact on employment, I believe,
should be on some of the designers.
Because now 3D is more helpful.
After designers design the style,
the original effect is two-dimensional.
But now, after we transform it into 3D,
designers can see the effect more directly.
So the new job opportunity is 3D Cloud.
I believe that in the future,
this expert will become a new profession.
It can open some new jobs for experts such as 3D consultants and 3D printers.
Training and education.
Yesterday and today,
a few professors and teachers have shared a lot.
They have also seen the importance of education and 3D.
I believe that these talents will continue to emerge.
Our foreign trade enterprises need to attract the attention of customers and the market.
Therefore, in product design and display,
we can have more competitiveness.
3D talents can use their technology
to innovate new products, models and brochures.
In this way,
companies can show and promote our products better.
The foreign trade industry also needs 3D talents
to use 3D technology and other technologies
to quickly develop and manufacture products.
This can help our companies
to improve productivity, quality and cost reduction.
3D talents can also create
visual effects and animations that impress people.
They can use them to promote products,
and wear them to videos, advertisements and shows.
In the market of fierce competition,
this visual presentation can help companies
attract more potential clients.
As virtual reality is exhausted,
and rapidly developed and applied real-time technologies are enhanced.
The foreign trade enterprises will use more and more of these technologies
to display and promote our products.
3D talents can use their technologies
to build соп PhD in virtual scenes and interactive experiences.
to provide a better shopping experience and product experience.
For example, our company will create a
men's and women's clothing, we can show different exhibition halls.
Every season, we can update our products
to better present the results of our different products to our customers.
From our company's perspective,
we summarize our needs for 3D talents.
Of course, 3D-acquired modeling software
can independently complete 3D modeling and modifications.
In fact, many 3D talents that we recruited before
may still have shortboards on the board,
so they all need help from the board master.
Maybe after the 3D model is built,
they need to make some modifications,
and the board master has to repeat it over and over again.
So in the future,
I believe that the 3D model
will need more knowledge
on how the CAD software is made,
how it is verified,
and how to modify the design of the clothing.
Moreover, we can use more
design software related to PSAI
to process the patterns and patterns.
We can also use more
software like CSD and Maya
to visualize and optimize
some of our overall animation software.
For our company,
when we recruit talents,
we will be in the TD department.
The TD department is more of a team
that examines the samples.
I will let the new recruits
to learn more about the craftsmanship of clothing.
First, they will learn about the craftsmanship of clothing,
the structure of clothing,
then they will learn about the design of clothing,
and then they will learn about 3D.
This will make our 3D talents
more comprehensive.
The 3D samples produced
can also meet the customer's standards.
Therefore, 3D talents
also need to be familiar with
the craftsmanship of clothing
and the craftsmanship of production.
Because when we were in school,
we could see more of
the 3D appearance
and design effects.
We could participate in
various competitions.
But our company
could use more
some of our clothing.
It's not just about the outside,
but also about my mind,
the details, the craftsmanship,
all of them need to simulate
the real sample.
So all of the craftsmanship
and production
require more 3D personnel,
need to be more familiar.
And also,
because we are a foreign trade company,
we need to have a good
English ability in clothing.
We can read, write, and listen.
For our company,
3D talents
can not only make 3D modeling.
They can go further,
go to the front,
and use professional language
to recommend and sell
our products to the customers.
We hope that
the staff
will have a more innovative spirit
and teamwork spirit.
They will love to learn,
love to experience,
and have a strong sense of responsibility.
They will have a good communication ability
and will be able to take on
some difficult projects.
And they can take on
these risks and responsibilities directly.
They will be able to understand
and predict the needs of
knowledge and technology.
And they will be able to understand
and push through more channels.
Our company is a good platform
that will help young people
to continue to learn and improve.
So our company has
a new journey,
a new dream,
a new startup,
a new breakthrough.
We gather people from all over the world
to join our business.
We hope that more people
can join us.
Thank you.